{
    "id": "057ba36dba5441e8a4b3a9d29e175325",
    "title": "Errors in the use of articles",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "38aa0ced9fe342348c05c8b71497ee8f",
            "title": "Articles Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "................................. is the capital of China.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Beijing",
                        "The Beijing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I first met your Dad at ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Walmart",
                        "the Walmart"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has failed in ....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "English",
                        "the English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She died of ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "malaria",
                        "the malaria"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is .......................................... singer I have heard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "best",
                        "the best"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The rose is ........................................ of all flowers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sweetest",
                        "the sweetest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... is mortal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "The man",
                        "Man",
                        "A man"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are in .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a trouble",
                        "the trouble",
                        "trouble"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are making ....................................... progress.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a rapid",
                        "rapid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is ..................................... scope for improvement.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a vast",
                        "vast",
                        "the vast"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your words are not worth ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "penny",
                        "a penny"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Donâ€™t make .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "noise",
                        "a noise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}